drgreene.com 2019-09-22

# Privacy Policy – DrGreene.com

## Your Privacy Is Important to Us!

Your privacy concerns are important to DrGreene.com. Our Privacy Policy is designed to protect your Personal Information while providing the services available on our website. You may use the DrGreene.com website without giving us specific Personal Information that identifies you.

## Your Personal Information

“Personal Information” includes, but is not limited to name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and similar information.

Personal Information is collected only if you voluntarily provide it on the website, however, certain information may be required to complete some services provided. If you do not wish to provide the information requested on a screen, or if you have concerns about maintaining the confidentiality of any information, do not provide it.

## Cookies on DrGreene.com

DrGreene.com uses cookies to uniquely identify users for the purpose of anonymous statistical information analysis and to track measure advertising.

## Third Party Services

DrGreene.com uses some third party software such as YouTube. They may also set cookies, but no personal information in these cookies is stored on DrGreene.com. You can choose to [opt out of certain cookies by visiting this page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/).

## How We Use Your Information

We will use Personal Information provided by you on a voluntary basis for the purpose for which it is given to us. It may be used by DrGreene.com, or by entities with which we contract for such purposes, which are disclosed at the time the information is given. If at any time you do not feel fully confident about the information you are providing, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.drgreene.com/contact-us).

## Sites We Link To Have Their Own Privacy Policy

If you visit a website linked to the DrGreene.com website, you should consult that website’s privacy policy before providing Personal Information.

## General Risks

In making your decision whether to provide Personal Information, you should be aware of the general risks of transmitting information over the Internet. While DrGreene.com attempts to prevent unauthorized persons from accessing or tampering with our website, we cannot guarantee that these efforts will always be successful.

## Children’s Privacy — We Don’t Collect Information from Children!

We do not collect any information from children, but if a parent learns that a child has submitted Personal Information to our website the parent should [contact us](http://www.drgreene.com/contact-us) and that information will be deleted.

This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with the [Terms of Service Agreement](http://www.drgreene.com/terms-of-use).
